ANS Record Group 2: Curatorial, 1858-ongoing
ANS Archives
ANS Record Group 2: Curatorial
1858-ongoing
Includes records relating to coins accessioned and held by the ANS, such as accession register log books, correspondence, wills, estate documents, unrestricted gift forms, card indexes, coin envelopes and related materials, as well as correspondence and other records produced and kept by ANS curators.
64.75 cubic feet
American Numismatic Society
PORTIONS OF THE FINDING AID ARE SUPPRESSED FROM PUBLIC VIEW. ANS staff can log into Staff View for the full record group description.
Organized into the following series: (1) Coin collection accession register log books, 1858-ongoing; (2) Coin collection card index, 1859-1904, bulk 1892-1901; (3) Coin collection accession records by accession number 1894, 1920-2004; (4) Coin collection accession records by subject and year, 1911-2007; (5) Coin collection deaccession records, 1958-2009; (6) Curatorial loan records, 1918-2007, bulk 1980-2007; (7) Exhibition records, 1900-2010; (8) Envelopes from Bates and Heaton coin collections, 1984-1985; (9) Howland Wood curator correspondence and other material; 1913-1937; (10) George C. Miles curator correspondence, research materials, and lectures, 1933-1974; (11) Henry Grunthal curator correspondence, 1967-1969; (12) Michael L. Bates curator correspondence and coin photographs, 1958-2004; (13) Jeremiah D. Brady curator correspondence, 1916-1981, bulk 1976-1979; (14) Nancy M. Waggoner curator correspondence and other material, 1968-1989; (15) Alan M. Stahl curator correspondence and other material, 1914-2000, bulk 1982-2000; (15) Carmen Arnold-Biucchi curator correspondence, 1982-1999; (16) Rose Chan Houston curator correspondence, 1947-1988; (17) William L. Bischoff curator correspondence, 1987; (18) William E. Metcalf curator correspondence, 1954-2000, bulk 1982-2000; (19) Miscellaneous collection records.
Parts of this finding aid, including descriptive notes and container lists, can only be viewed by logging in to Staff View.
Access
Portions are closed to outside researchers.
- Series 1: Coin collection accession register log books, 1858-ongoing; 3 cubic feet (7 bound items)
  Portions are closed to outside researchers.
  Accession registers; Logs (Records)
  Consists of seven coin collection accession register log books, in which are listed accession number, date, a brief description, country, denomination, material, donor or seller, and cost. The level of descriptive detail among the entries varies. These books have been the official record of accessions since the Society’s founding in 1858.
  - Book 1: 1858-1904
  - Book 2: 1904-1911
  - Book 3: 1911-1921
  - Book 4: 1922-1932
  - Book 5: 1933-1937
  - Book 6: 1938-1971
  - Book 7: 1972-ongoing
- Series 2: Coin collection card index, 1859-1904, bulk 1892-1901; 0.5 cubic feet (5 boxes)
  Open to all researchers.
  Saltus, J. Sanford, 1853-1922; Sage, Augustus B., 1842-1874; Card indexes; Parish, Daniel, 1842-1914
  Card index with detailed descriptions of various donated coins, sometimes including donor and date acquired, or indicating whether purchased along with price. Donors include Augustus B. Sage, Daniel Parish Jr., and J. Sanford Saltus.
- Series 3: Coin collection accession records by accession number, 1894, 1920-2004; 2.5 cubic feet (3 boxes)
  Users should also consult the following series in the Curatorial record group (RG2 [this record group]): Coin Collection Accession Records by Subject and Year.
  Users searching for cash and other donations should also consult the following series in the record group Development and Membership (RG3): (1) Donation Files and (2) Wills, Bequests, Gifts, and Special Funds Records.
  Estate records; Wills; Lists (Document genres); Clippings (Information artifacts); Correspondence; Chase Manhattan Bank Money Museum
  Contains a variety of coin collection accession records, such as acknowledgment letters, other correspondence, and unrestricted gift forms. Not all of the files contain the same types of records. Some contain materials such as wills, estate inventories, clippings, and coin lists. The “1980.66-1980.67 – Chase Manhattan Bank Money Museum” file has correspondence relating to an 1804 silver dollar, and includes the earliest materials in the series, an 1894 letter relating to the dollar.
  - Box 1 of 3
    - 1920.147 – William R. Powell
    - 1921.57 – W.H. Valentine
    - 1922.184 – Walter Thorn
    - 1930.11 – Arthur T. Walker
    - 1937.56 – Arthur C. Wyman
    - 1937.158 – J.C. Lawrence (Mrs. Richard Hoe Lawrence)
    - 1937.177 – De Witt Clinton Falls
    - 1937.179 – John Reilly Jr.
    - 1938 – V.D. Starosselsky
    - 1939 – Edmund Zygman
    - 1940.88 – John F. Jones
    - 1943-1945 – David Bullowa
    - 1944 – Alexandre Orlowski
    - 1946.143 – George H. Clapp
    - 1947 – Wayte Raymond
    - 1948.90 – Bernard Morgenthau
    - 1949 – James A. Brown
    - 1950.122 – Wayte Raymond – with summary of gifts, 1930-1950
    - 1951.116 (see 1953.87 – Gunther)
    - 1952.142 (see 1953.87 – Gunther)
    - 1952.196 (see 1953.87 – Gunther)
    - 1953.30 (see 1953.87 – Gunther)
    - 1953.87 – Christian G. Gunther (3 files)
    - 1953.87 – Christian G. Gunther (3 files)
    - 1954.53-1954.57 – Coin World – J. Oliver Amos
    - 1954.237 – Herbert E. Ives
    - 1955.54 – Jean B. Cammann
    - 1957.172 – Hoyt Miller
    - 1961.2 – Mrs. R. Henry Norweb
    - 1961.136 – Mrs. R. Henry Norweb
    - 1967.225 and 1967.226 – Wadsworth Atheneum – J. Coolidge Hills collection
    - 1969.9 – Leo N. Kukuranov
    - 1969.83 – Wilbert C. When
    - 1969.222 – P.K. Anderson (Paul Kenneth)
    - 1971.49 (see 1973.37 – Newman)
    - 1971.316 (see 1973.37 – Newman)
    - 1971.250 – Ruth M. Keller
    - 1972.79 (see 1973.37 – Newman)
    - 1972.288 (see 1973.37 – Newman)
    - 1973.37 – Eric P. Newman (Robert W. Morris collection)
    - 1974.260 – Paul Balog
    - 1977.77-1977.101 – Lloyd Cabot Briggs
    - 1977.158 – Robert F. Kelley
    - 1977.188 – Frederick S. Werner
    - 1979.45 – William F. Spengler
    - 1980.43 – Goldberg – Superior Stamp
    - 1980.66-1980.67 – Chase Manhattan Bank Money Museum
    - 1980.149 (see 1982.175 – Spengler)
    - 1984 – Darwin Palmer
    - 1984.146 – Pierre Bastien
    - 1985.81 – Daniel M. Friedenberg
    - 1986.28 – Joseph R. Lasser
    - 1986.99 (Haiti), 1986.100 (World coins) – Robert L. Saxe
    - 1986.176 – Roger Linscott
    - 1987.31 – Robert H. Lloyd
    - 1987.98 – George W. Ball – CSA Bonds
    - 1987.104, 1987.105, 1987.106, 1987.110 – Neil S. Berman
    - 1987.165 – Charles K. Panish
    - 1987.169 – Robert L. Saxe
    - 1987.186 – Frank L. Kovacs
    - 1988.71 – George Lill III
    - 1988.107 – George Lill III
    - 1988.21 – Charles K. Panish
    - 1988.84 – Charles K. Panish
    - 1988.91 – Charles K. Panish
    - 1988.143 – Charles K. Panish
    - 1988.149 – Charles K. Panish
    - 1988.166 – R. Henry Norweb – St. Patrick forgery
    - 1989.8 – Miguel Estrella Gomez
    - 1989.10 – Charles K. Panish
    - 1989.18 – Herbert J. Erlanger
    - 1989.30 – Jan Lis
    - 1989.38 – R. Henry Norweb, Jr.
    - 1989.67 – William S. Kable
    - 1989.71 – George Lill III
    - 1989.83 – William S. Kable
    - 1989.110 – Gateway Coin Club
    - 1989.119 – Intel Corporation
    - 1989.120 – William S. Kable
    - 1990.3 – Peter Burbules
    - 1990.4 – Anthony Terranova
    - 1990.10 – Vincent Zecchino
    - 1990.11 – Foundation for Numismatic Research
    - 1990.12 – Museo de la Fabrica Nacional de Moneda y Timbre
    - 1990.13 – Scott Miller
    - 1990.14 – Charles Hersh
    - 1990.15 – Presidential Coin and Antique
    - 1990.25 – Heifetz sale – Superior Stamp and Coin
    - 1990.28 – Scott Miller
    - 1990.30 – Jay Galst
    - 1990.32 – Society of Medalists
    - 1990.33 – William T. Rumph (vendor)
    - 1990.37 – Jiri Harcuba
    - 1990.38 – Society of Medalists
    - 1990.42 – Gabriel Austin
    - 1990.52 – George Bates
    - 1990.53 – Gordon Andreas Singer (vendor)
    - 1990.54 – Paul Bosco (vendor)
    - 1990.61 – Busso Peus (vendor)
    - 1990.71 – Wayne Sayles
    - 1990.74 – H. Elliot Rogers
    - 1990.75 – Holli Schwartz
    - 1990.79 – Robert Gobl
    - 1990.80 – Jay Galst
    - 1990.81 – Gravarte Gravadores
    - 1990.82 – Joseph Veach Noble
    - 1990.83 – Eva Varga
    - 1990.84 – Gerard Muhl
    - 1990.85 – American Medallic Sculpture (vendor)
    - 1990.87 – Scott Miller
    - 1990.88 – Marie H. Martin
    - 1990.90 – Gateway Coin Club
    - 1990.91 – Russell Rulau
    - 1990.95 – David R. Lit
    - 1990.96 – Robert Weinman
    - 1990.97 – Alan Stahl
    - 1990.98 – Mark Jones (vendor)
    - 1990.101 – William S. Kable
    - 1990.105 – Serge Huard
    - 1990. 106 – Bourne Historical Society (vendor)
    - 1990.107 – Vincent Zecchino
    - 1991.1 to 1991.150
      (Note: Beginning in 1991, most files have the accession number only.)
  - Box 2 of 3
    - 1992.2 to 1999.77
  - Box 3 of 3
    - 2000.1 to 2008.51
- Series 4: Coin collection accession records by subject and year, 1911-2007; 1 cubic foot (1 box)
  Users should also consult the following series in the Curatorial record group (RG2 [this record group]): Coin Collection Accession Records by Accession Number.
  Correspondence; Shipping records; Lists; Inventories
  Contains a variety of records including correspondence, shipping documents, coin lists and inventories, invoices, import and export licenses (1962-1968), and other materials relating to coins, medals, and other numismatic materials that were accessioned, offered, or otherwise considered of interest to the Society. In some cases the relevant accession number is written on the document. The series is a somewhat ad hoc gathering of materials relating to accessions that were filed in different ways over time, and includes stray files not easily placed elsewhere.
  - Box 1 of 1
    - Khlifes Omeyyades – Islamic collection, 1911?
    - Huntington Gift – Paper money in book, additions from collections, 1915
    - Charles Joseph Ready collection, 1920
    - R.B. Whitehead – Collection of Indian coins, 1921
    - Spink and Sons – Bills, receipts, and correspondence, 1919-1929
    - Bills, notes, tickets, and correspondence re coin purchases, 1923-1930
    - Bekir Nuzhet - Islamic collection, 1928
    - Raymond S. Saltoun – regarding 1928 donation, 1935
    - Gift acknowledgements, 1937, 1939
    - Islamic and Roman – Materials for coin labeling, 1939
    - Three years of the Newell Collection: A report to the curator, 1940-1947
    - Various, 1921-1954
    - Various, 1939
    - Various, 1940
    - Various, 1941
    - Various, 1942
    - Various, 1943
    - Various, 1943
    - Various, 1944-1948
    - Various 1948
    - Various, 1949
    - Various, 1950
    - Various, 1950-1952
    - Various, 1951
    - U.S. Decorations – Purchase, 1943-1946
    - Warren A. Baker – First Class Medal for Civilian Defense, 1945
    - Photographs - 1949
    - Accessions listed by committee subject area, 1962-1963
    - Record of Gifts, 1951-1968
    - Gold and silver import/export licenses, 1962-1968
    - Balance sheets, 1971-1978
    - Various, 1976-1977
    - Purchases pending and gifts, 1981-1996
    - Miguel Munoz, Hill collection, Paul P. Rugg, 1984
    - Lost coins – including Suros, 1989
    - Mark M. Salton, Bank Leu, British Art Medal Trust, Munzen and Medaileen, Brian Wall, 1991
    - Paul Rynearson, 1991-1994
    - 1980 Accessions – Alan Stahl
    - 1981 Medals – Alan Stahl
    - 1981 Medieval – Alan Stahl
    - 1981 Purchase records – Alan Stahl
    - 1982 Medals and decorations – Alan Stahl
    - 1982 Medieval – Alan Stahl
    - 1982 Purchase records – Alan Stahl
    - 1983 Medals – Alan Stahl
    - 1983 Medieval – Alan Stahl
    - 1983 Purchase records – Alan Stahl
    - 1984 Coins – Alan Stahl
    - 1984 Medals – Alan Stahl
    - 1984 Purchases – Alan Stahl
    - 1985 Coins – Alan Stahl
    - 1985 Medals – Alan Stahl
    - 1985 Purchases – Alan Stahl
    - 1986 Decorations – Alan Stahl
    - 1986 Medals – Alan Stahl
    - 1986 Medieval – Alan Stahl
    - 1987 Purchases – Alan Stahl
    - 1988 Decorations inquiries – Alan Stahl
    - 1988 Medals and decorations – Alan Stahl
    - 1988 Medieval – Alan Stahl
    - 1988 Purchases – Alan Stahl
    - 1989 Medals – Alan Stahl
    - 1989 Purchases – Alan Stahl
    - 2002 – Donations to the collection
    - 2003 – E.C. Hubert – DuPont Medallion – Possible donation
    - 2003 – Donations to the collection
    - 2004 – Donations to the collection
    - 2005 – Acquisitions
    - 2005 – Gifts/Donations to the collection
    - 2006 – Col. Alvan Markle – Numismatic Antiquarian Society of Philadelphia – Possible Donation
    - 2006 – Collections
    - 2007 – Tangible gifts
- Series 5: Coin collection deaccession records, 1958-2009; 1 cubic foot (1 box)
  Correspondence; Lists (Document genres); Auction catalogs
  Correspondence, auction catalogs, lists of coins to be auctioned, and disposition forms, all relating to the deaccessioning and disposition of duplicate and otherwise undesirable items in the collections.
  - Box 1 of 1
    - Disposition of Duplicates – Hoyt Miller Collection, 1958, 1959, 1960
    - Disposition of Duplicates, 1954, 1955, 1959
    - Duplicates sold, 1971-1972
    - Disposition of Duplicates, 10/1/64 – 8/18/74
    - Disposition of Duplicates, 7/15/65 – 9/11/74
    - Disposition of Duplicates, 9/11/74 – 9/12/75
    - Libertas Americana – Sale of duplicates, 1976
    - Disposition of Duplicates, 11/7/75 – 11/5/76
    - Disposition of Duplicates, 11/5/76 – 9/9/77
    - Disposition of Duplicates, 11/11/77 – 11/11/78
    - Disposition of Duplicates, 1/11/86 – 10/15/88
    - Disposition of Duplicates, 1/14/89 – 12/31/96
    - Disposals, 1982
    - Dispositions, 1988
    - Dispositions, 1989
    - Disposition of Duplicates, 1993
    - Morton & Eden – Shipping and returned items, 2006, 2009
    - Proposal for Sale: The Collection of Orders and Decorations of The American Numismatic Society (printed item), Christie’s in association with Spink, 2005
    - Three CD-ROMs and printout of computer database: ANS medals, orders, and decorations, 2006
    - Auction catalogs: Medals, Orders and Decorations from the Collection of the American Numismatic Society, Morton & Eden, volumes 1,2, and 3, 2006 (3 copies each)
    - Auction catalog: United States Gold Coins from the American Numismatic Society Collection, 101 Die Duplicates, Stack’s, 2007 (3 copies)
    - Auction catalog: Ancient World Coins (includes ANS duplicates), Gemini, 2009 (1 copy)
- Series 6: Curatorial loan records, 1918-2007, bulk 1980-2007; 6 cubic feet (7 boxes and 1 loose item)
  Primarily organized into incoming (loans received) and outgoing (loans to other institutions). Portions of the records are arranged roughly chronologically or alphabetically, but overall the records appear to be unarranged.
  Agreements; Insurance records; Photographs; Correspondence; Agreements; Lists (Document genres); Exhibition records; Exhibition catalogs; Brochures
  Contains records pertaining to materials lent to ANS by other institutions (incoming loans), and items loaned out to other institutions by ANS (outgoing loans). Records on incoming loans include signed deposit agreements, certificates of insurance, lists of loaned items, photographs (occasionally), correspondence, and materials such as label texts relating to exhibits held at ANS. Records pertaining to outgoing loans include correspondence, facility reports from receiving institutions, certificates of insurance, printed materials such as brochures and exhibit catalogs from borrowing institutions, shipping documentation, loan request forms, photographs (occasionally), and lists of loaned items. Materials were most often loaned for exhibit, but in some cases were loaned for testing, as in the case of glass weights sent to be analyzed (but were not actually studied) at Corning Museum of Glass (1983, 1993) and items sent for microprobe analysis at the University of Illinois (1990). Also present are files on a theft of shipped ANS coins in an armed robbery at a post office in 1990; materials returned to the University of Pennsylvania (1939-2001); an album containing photographs of The Gwynne M. Andrews Collection loaned by the Metropolitan Museum of Art, February 16, 1931, along with images of coins loaned in 1930, 1935, 1936; the loan of the Bechtler coin press to The Mint Museum, Charlotte, North Carolina, from 1978 to 1991; a long-term loan from the New Jersey Historical Society of the Frederick Canfield numismatic collection, held at ANS from 1931 to 1994; and the buy-back of coins on long term loan to the ANS by the Metropolitan Museum of Art that were scheduled to be auctioned in 1973. The earliest materials are those pertaining to an ANS loan to the New-York Historical Society (1918).
  - Box 1 of 7: Incoming Loans
    - John Flanagan collection on indefinite loan, 1954
    - Richard Doty collection, 1974
    - George Cuhaj collection, 1981
    - William E. Metcalf collection, 1986
    - Deposits, 1950-1973
    - Deposits, 1974
    - Deposits, 1975
    - Deposits, 1976
    - Deposits, 1977
    - Deposits, 1978
    - Deposits, 1979
    - Deposits, 1980
    - Deposits – Private collections now with ANS, 1969-1981
    - Deposits, 1981
    - Deposits, 1982
    - Deposits, 1983
    - Deposits, 1984
    - Deposits, 1985
    - Deposits - John L. Dresser collection, 1986
    - Deposits, 1987
    - Deposits, 1988
    - Deposits, 1989
    - Deposits, 1990
    - Deposits, 1991
    - Deposits, 1994
    - Deposits, 1996
    - Loan to ANS – University of Missouri, Columbia, 1983
    - Loan to ANS – Dorothy B. Moore (Pisanello Medal), 1995
    - Loan to ANS – Oriental Institute, 1975
    - Various long-term loans to the ANS (includes John Flanagan)
    - Loan to ANS – Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, – Completed, 1965-1976
    - General Services Administration, Utililization and Donation Division, 1975-1980
    - Material temporarily deposited with the ANS, 1991-1992
    - Material temporarily deposited with the ANS, 1986
    - Completed – Karen Worth exhibit, 1979-1980
    - Completed – Finnish Medal exhibit, 1976
    - Katherine M. Edwards collection taken from ANS by estate official, 1953
    - Dwight D. Eisenhower (Columbia University president), 1950
    - Loan to ANS – Marcel Jovine, 1985
    - Loan to ANS – William J. Bareford, 1979
    - Academy & Institute of Arts and Letters – COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1987
    - Private collections formerly with ANS, 1969-1973
    - Completed – T.V. Buttrey, Jr., 1985
    - Loan completed – Jonathan Kagan, 1988
    - Completed – Robert Vlack, 1986
    - Completed – Donald P. Partrick, 1984
    - Temporary deposits returned, fiscal 1993
    - Completed – Newark Museum, 1985
    - Completed – U.S. Mint – COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1984
    - Completed – COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1985
    - Material temporarily deposited – Returned, 1994
    - Material temporarily deposited – Returned, fiscal 1992
    - Thomas C. Wilfred, 1988
    - Cynthia Kennedy Sam – COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1987
    - Saint Gaudens National Historic Site, New Hampshire – COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1987
    - Newark Museum – COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1987
    - National Museum of American Art, Smithsonian Institution – COAC,1987
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston – COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1987
    - Scott Miller – COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1987
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art – COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1987
    - William Koch coin deposit – Cancelled, 1987-1988
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1987
    - George Ewing – Temporary deposit, 1987
    - Corning Museum, 1989
    - John Cook – Exhibit and loan, 1988
    - Janis Conner – COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference), 1987
    - Coins returned to owners – Receipts, 1988
    - COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference) – Exhibitors, 1988
    - James Bogardus project, 1989
    - Request for Beaux Arts extension, 1988
    - Loan to ANS – National Museum of American History, 1987
    - Loan to ANS – Metropolitan Museum – Japanese medals, 1990
    - Exhibit – The Japanese Medal, 1990
    - Norweb tokens – Loaned to ANS for use at the British Museum, 1975
  - Box 2 of 7: Incoming Loans (continued)
    - Loans and deposits of Islamic and South Asian material in the ANS (notebook), 1972-1975
    - Stephen Scher, 1998
    - Saltus award – Mico Kaufman, 1992
    - Saltus, 1994
    - Saltus, 1995 (1 of 2)
    - Saltus, 1995 (2 of 2)
    - Saltus, 1996
    - Saltus – Nikola Moss, 1996
    - Saltus, 1998
    - Saltus, 1999
    - Saltus, 2000
    - Saltus - Bernd Göbel, 1999-2000
    - Saltus, 2001 (1 of 2)
    - Saltus, 2001 (2 of 3)
    - Saltus, 2001 (3 of 3)
    - Saltus, 2001 – Gustaaf T.M. Hellegers (includes photographs), 2001
    - Saltus, 2002
    - Huntington Award – John Davenport, 1999
    - Byzantine exhibit, 2000
    - Byzantine exhibit – Case 1 – The Turks in History, 2000
    - COAC (Coinage of the Americas Conference) – Medals exhibit, 1997
    - Temporary deposit, 1999-2007
    - Temporary deposit return, 1996-2007
    - Temporary deposit (includes Bicentennial, 1976, and coins lost by Anthony B. Garvan, 1981), 1973-1981
    - Eric P. Newman Bicentennial loan correspondence, 1976
    - Bicentennial loans – Newmann, et al., 1972
    - James H. Charlesworth, 2004-2006
    - Loan to ANS – Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1985-2000
    - University of Pennsylvania Museum of Archaeology & Anthropology, 1939-2001
    - University of Pennsylvania Museum of Archaeology & Anthropology – Loan return, 2001
    - Temporary deposits – Returned, fiscal 1994
    - Temporary deposits – Return, 1995-1996
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1994
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) - Ferrari, 1995
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) - Ferrari, 1996
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 1997
    - Leonda Finke, 1997
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille) - Ferrari, 1995
    - FIDEM (Fédération Internationale de la Médaille), 2000
  - Box 3 of 7: Outgoing Loans
    - Phoenix Art Museum – Renaissance of Islam, 1981-1982
    - Asia House Gallery, 1977-1979
    - Museum of Art and Archaeology, Columbia-Missouri, 1987
    - DePauw University – Leslie Cornell, 1987
    - American Academy and Institute, 1978
    - New York Numismatic Convention – Metropolitan Museum – Saint-Gaudens, 1987
    - Harvard University Art Museum, 1986
    - American Numismatic Association, 1986-1987
    - Eastern Michigan University – Giles Carter, 1987
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1986-1987
    - American Museum of National History, 1979
    - Asia Society, 1986
    - Frick Collection, 1985
    - Balzekas Museum of Lithuanian Culture, 1983
    - Cooper Hewitt Museum, 1984-1985
    - DeLuca and LaCapra, 1979
    - Washington State Capital Museum, 1988
    - National Museums of Canada, 1979-1984
    - New-York Historical Society, 1984-1985
    - North Carolina Museum of History, 1984
    - National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian Institution, 1985
    - DePauw University, 1985
    - (note from Lori to Bill regarding these files, found loose here)
    - Division of Archives, Florida Department of State, 1984
    - Dog Museum of America, 1982
    - Eastern Michigan University, 1981
    - Edith Blum Art Institute, 1986
    - Field Museum of Natural History, 1980
    - Garvies Point Museum, Nassau County, N.Y. – The Indian, 1978
    - Grolier Club, 1979
    - Hammond Castle Museum, 1982
    - Harley School – Wilson Arts Center, 1979
    - Islamic XVI Centennial, 1981-1982
    - Frank L. Kovacs, 1985
    - Museum of Archaeology at Staten Island, 1981
    - Museum of Fine Arts, 1982